[theme music playing]
[Ivy] Raul tipped him off
that the Ardientes know
where the safe house is.
[Jepoy] I'll handle that, Ivy.
I'll find out.
[Raul] What's important is
she's ready for the Ardientes.
Dad, you might get in trouble for this.
I can help Camia more
if I stay here with the Ardientes.
[Emilia] You traitor!
I will find out who you're working with!
[Arnaldo] If you still want to
see your daughter alive,
you'll come see me.
[Tonio] Have you seen Esther
and Edward around?
We've been looking for them all day.
[Camia] Esther and Edward are in danger.
Not just them, but all our witnesses.
[Noel] What's going on?
Have the Ardientes found us?
[Tonio] I bet Edward and Esther
ratted us out.
[Arnaldo] Break down the door!
Leave no one alive!
[gunshots]
[Gino] Let's focus on the issue here.
Camia Cruz. Is what she's saying true?
These are all false allegations.
Think about it.
What father could ever kill
his own children?
And to my children in Ardiente,
you know the truth.
Your Señor Julio loves you.
-Ivy, they're not there.
-[Ivy] We have to secure Tonio.
Tonio escaped, Grandpa.
We don't know who helped him.
[Julio] Clean up your mother's mess.
[Camia] Your men called me.
Lily, they're all dead.
[screams]
[Ivy] After everything we've done!
Mayor. Everything you want
to know about Tonio
and his family is in here.
[Georgina] The prosecution
calls Mr. Antonio Vidal
to the witness stand.
Did former governor Emilia Torillo
order you to rape and kill Camia Cruz?
[Tonio] No, your Honor.
[tense music playing]
Let me remind you, Mr. Vidal.
You released a statement
saying Mrs. Torillo ordered you.
Are you telling us you lied?
Yes, your Honor. I lied.
I'm taking back my statement.
[Georgina] Lying under oath
is a very serious offense, Mr. Vidal.
You can go to jail.
I'm sorry.
Did someone order you
to change your testimony?
Did someone threaten your life?
[tense music playing]
No one did. This was my own decision.
I just wanted to extort money
from the Ardientes…
but I feel guilty now.
I'm retracting my first statement.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
"Hi, baby!"
Ma'am, I'll go out for a while.
[Tonio's wife] Okay.
Sweetie, finish that up so we can sleep.
Okay.
[beeping sound]
[tense music playing]
"It's Daddy. I miss you!"
[Rosalie] What?
Why did Daddy make a new account?
[beeping sound]
[Rosalie] IS THIS A NEW ACCOUNT?
[Arnaldo] THIS IS MY SECRET
ACCOUNT. DON'T TELL ANYONE.
[Arnaldo] I WANNA SEE YOU.
WHERE ARE YOU? PLEASE!
Hello? Baby? Hey.
[Tonio] Why did you call?
[Tonio's wife] I'm begging you!
Please let us go!
We've done nothing wrong!
Daddy T. Where are you?
I miss you so much.
Who are you?
Didn't I tell you I'd find you?
Where's my daughter? Where's my family?
You want to talk
to your daughter? Here she is.
-Daddy!
-Tonio!
-Help us!
-Rosalie!
…Daddy!
-Tonio…
-Rosalie!
[Tonio's wife] I'm begging you!
-Help me!
-So… Are we good?
Is that okay? Now…
if you still want them to live,
you'll do exactly as I say.
Do you understand?
Okay.
I'll do anything you want.
Just please don't hurt my family.
That's what I wanted to hear.
Tonio!
No one told me to do this.
I'm just telling the truth,
so I can clear my conscience.
[ominous music playing]
Governor Torillo never ordered
me to rape and kill Camia Cruz.
The Ardientes never ordered me
to kill anyone.
[Emilia] Ivy!
[Emilia] I'm so happy the truth
is finally out.
-Yes, congratulations, Emilia.
-I know!
Thank you! Thank you.
Papa.
[sinister music playing]
The Ardientes would've killed my family…
if I didn't retract my statement.
But I didn't rat you out, Miss Ivy.
I owe so much to you.
I already owe you my life.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Please forgive me.
Diego…
Did you say anything to your father?
No. Believe me, I wouldn't do that.
[tense music playing]
I know.
[Carlotta] But how did this happen?
You did it, Arnaldo.
Not that I had any doubts.
But you've secured a victory
for us in this legal battle.
Of course, Grandpa.
Like you said. Failure is not an option.
[scoffs]
Here's to you.
[sinister music playing]
[soft music playing]
This isn't over, Mom.
Whatever happens in court…
win or lose, this isn't over.
I will continue to fight.
[somber music playing]
Due to insufficient testimonies
and evidence submitted in court,
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo and Raul Torillo…
are hereby declared innocent of the rape,
abduction, and illegal imprisonment
of Camia Cruz.
[Ardiente allies applauding]
[gavel banging]
[woman] Wonderful news.
[tense music playing]
Gentlemen…
to the victor belong the spoils!
-Cheers!
-Congratulations!
Congratulations, Papa!
You dodged that bullet.
Right. You know, Emilia…
I never once felt worried
about the lawsuit.
Because I knew that my favorite
grandson would find a way.
[emphatic] Arnaldo, you are the man!
If not for you…
your parents would've been imprisoned now…
and all of us Ardientes would
have lost our reputation.
I told you I'd find
that bastard, didn't I?
This is your best work yet, my grandson.
I'm very proud of you.
Thank you. Who else would I take after?
I learned from the best.
-Well… Cheers!
-[all] Cheers!
-To Mayor Arnaldo!
-Cheers!
-Daddy!
-[ecstatic] Rosalie!
As agreed, I have your family with me.
All of your passports are here.
You'll be in Thailand tomorrow morning.
Everything you need to know
about the trip is in that envelope.
Thank you, Miss Ivy.
[tense music playing]
Unlike you, Tonio,
I'm always true to my word.
[tense music playing]
It's going to be tough
to bring down the Ardientes.
We need help from the opposition.
What about Senator Magno?
Nanny, we need to be more careful.
They have their own personal
and political agendas.
We can't just trust them so easily.
[Jepoy] Leave that to me, Ivy.
I'll get all Senator Magno's papers
at the Ardientes' mansion.
We're running out of time.
I'll also get the camera
I hid in Julio's room.
I'm sure we can get some evidence from it.
Jepoy.
You need to be careful.
The Ardientes are more cautious now.
Don't make a move
unless you're sure about it.
[phone ringing]
[line ringing]
Diego?
-Ivy, it's about to start.
-Thank you.
Nanny, the TV.
[sinister music playing]
[reporter] Miss Camia's here.
Miss Camia, any comments?
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[reporter] What's your message
for the Ardientes?
[indistinct chatter]
[reporter] What's your next move?
Is it true that you had an affair
with Mr. Raul Torillo?
We all know why the case
against the Ardientes
was dismissed.
Because they threatened
and had the witnesses killed
so no one could prove
the crimes they committed.
[Camia] Well… I'm not afraid of them.
[sinister music playing]
And they can't stop me
from seeking justice
for what they did to me.
For killing my husband
and hundreds of other innocent people.
I may have lost this battle,
but I will win the war.
[Camia] It's just the beginning.
And I won't stop until I expose
all the Ardientes dirty secrets!
-[man] Viva Ardiente!
-[woman] Viva Ardiente!
-Mom.
-Viva Ardiente!
-[Diego] Miss Camia, let's go.
-[all] Viva Ardiente!
-[woman] You're despicable!
-[man] We won the case!
[reporter] Any message
to the supporters of Ardientes?
[Ardientes' supporters]
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
[sinister music playing]
[Ivy] Mom! Mom!
Ivy.
Mom, are you all right? Are you hurt?
How about you, Diego?
We're both fine now.
The one who threw a rock
at Mrs. Camia was apprehended.
An Ardiente loyalist.
I better tighten the security, then.
You don't have to.
What matters is Diego and I are safe.
No, I have to do it.
Espiritu, I want guard dogs.
I want you to set checkpoints up
at every corner. Is that clear?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Do it right now!
As I said, Mom,
your safety is my top priority.
I'm glad you're okay.
Diego, thank you.
[Julio] What do you mean, Arnaldo?
Tonio was able to leave
the country without us knowing?
Grandpa, I had Tonio and
his family closely monitored.
But someone helped them.
So, they managed to escape.
The question is, who?
Camia doesn't have
the resources to do that.
Well, whoever it was,
they're obviously
powerful enough to do it.
I'm suspecting Senator Magno,
but we're not sure yet.
How can we make sure Tonio
will keep quiet?
-That he won't appear again?
-I doubt it.
After I threatened Tonio and his family…
I'm sure he'll keep his mouth shut.
One more slip-up, and I'll wipe them out.
Just like how I took care
of all the other witnesses.
Good. As for me,
I'll silence Camia once and
for all to solve our problem.
Slow down, Emilia.
We managed to remain Scot-free
after having those witnesses killed.
But Camia Cruz…
She's too high a risk to take right now.
And the media has its eyes on us.
As long as that's the case,
we can't touch Camia Cruz.
For now, what we should do…
is make sure they won't get
any more witnesses to help them.
And, Emilia… You better watch Raul.
He's crazy over Camia Cruz.
Make sure he isn't betraying us.
Yes, Papa.
I'm sorry, but you can't come here.
I just want to talk to Camia.
I'm sorry, but you can't do that.
-I just want to talk to her!
-Sir.
-Stop, sir.
-Camia! Camia!
-Camia!
-You have to…
-to leave, sir.
-Camia! Come out now!
Camia! Wait!
-You have to leave, sir.
-Ouch!
Wait! Ouch! Hey! Camia! Camia!
-Camia! Hey!
-You can't go here, sir.
Who is that? What's going on?
Ma'am, someone's causing a scene outside.
-Who?
-It's Raul Torillo.
You know what to do.
Don't you ever let him set foot in here.
Yes, ma'am.
[tense music playing]
Raul isn't in his room.
But don't worry. I had someone follow him.
[tense music playing]
I just want to talk to you!
Wait. Wait. Camia!
-Sir, please.
-Camia, please talk to me!
I want to know if you're safe!
Last warning, sir. Leave.
You know how much I love you! Camia!
[dog barking]
Last warning, sir. You should leave now.
[tense music playing]
[phone dings]
[Raul] Camia, you know
how much I love you!
Camia, talk to me!
[guard] Sir, you have to leave.
[Raul] Camia!
[scoffs]
So you love her?
[tense music playing]
[nervously exhales]
[door opening]
[sinister music playing]
Madrigal.
What are you doing in my office?
Congressman, the nurse asked me
to bring your medicine here.
I'm sorry.
All right. You may leave now.
[sinister music playing]
[line ringing]
Hello, Arnaldo.
Keep an eye on Madrigal.
[somber music playing]
Why are you awake? Why aren't you in bed?
Well, I'm just having
a few drinks. Care to join me?
No, thanks. Well then…
Where've you been?
[tense music playing]
I was with some of my business partners.
We talked about some new plans.
Good night.
Such a terrible liar.
[phone ringing]
Lily, what's wrong?
Mom, I'm in the car behind you.
Do you really need to come here?
Lily, why did you follow me?
Someone might see you.
-Mom.
-Lily, dear.
Our supporters organized…
this event.
They're victims of the Ardientes too.
I want to support them.
Mom, I understand that.
But every time you leave the house…
I can't help but worry about you.
Lily, I can't just sit there all the time.
We're in this together,
regardless of the danger we're facing.
Even if you surround me
with a hundred bodyguards,
we can't always be safe.
But we shouldn't be afraid
because if we are, we'll lose the fight.
Okay, Mom.
Don't worry. I'll be with Diego.
-Okay.
-Okay, bye.
[ominous music playing]
Let's go.
[action music playing]
Mrs. Camia, no one's here yet.
[goon] Freeze! Nobody move!
Nobody move! Hands up!
[goon] Hands up!
Let go of me!
[thud]
Stop it!
Who sent you here?
Stop the car!
Emilia…
[tense music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
[door closes]
Hi, my dear Camia! Camia, Camia, darling!
[Emilia sighs]
Let go of her.
Look at you.
You're so beautiful.
And you smell nice!
[laughs]
Oh, Diego.
No wonder my husband is crazy about you.
You're like an angel sent from heaven!
Not once in my life have I ever
been interested in your husband.
I'm never going to steal him from you!
He's all yours!
Stick it in that brain of yours!
Wow! Thanks, darling!
That's very comforting!
But we still have a problem.
Because whatever I do to Raul…
my husband is addicted to you.
-That's your problem!
-It's my problem, your problem,
my husband's problem,
it's everyone's problem!
You know, my efforts to hurt Raul
have no effect on him.
But what if I hurt you?
Will he come to his senses?
Do whatever you want to do.
You had me raped once,
and you had me buried alive.
There's nothing else
I have to fear from you!
[teasing] Wow! Bravo, bravo!
You're so brave! That's what I love!
And true, you've faced
death before, right?
Whoops. Almost.
What if this time, I bring you closer?
Close? She's standing right
in front of me now!
Hmm?
Closer? This is close!
Let go of me!
Do you want more? More?! More?!
[Camia laughs]
You know, Emilia, you're so funny.
Because no matter what you do,
your husband doesn't respect you.
And I know that
even if you have me killed now,
your husband will never love you!
So you really want more?!
You monster!
Murderer! Murderer!
-[Ivy] Emilia!
-[Diego] Mrs. Camia, stop!
Let go of me! Hey!
That's enough! Emilia, that's enough!
Ouch.
What on earth are you doing?!
You're causing another scandal!
What will your father,
the Congressman, say?
What will the people of Ardiente say?
You're at it again.
You just had your lawsuit dismissed.
What else do you want? A reunion in court?
[tense music playing]
And what the hell are you doing here?
[suspenseful sting]
[tense music playing]
I saw you on the way here.
And I wanted to come in and say hi.
And… wow, Emilia. I sure was surprised.
[sighs]
What's with that look?
Are you actually suspecting me?
I couldn't care less about this woman.
But, you… Aren't we friends?
I'm just concerned about you, Emilia.
Oops. I'm sorry again.
[laughing]
[tense music playing]
Mom.
How many times do I have to tell you
that I can take care of myself?
Mom…
You can't stop me from worrying.
From worrying that I'll lose you again.
Mom, I was just a kid when
they first took you from me.
I couldn't do anything.
But it's different now.
So I can't stop myself from protecting you
when they're hurting you
right in front of me!
But I won't allow you
to get hurt in exchange for protecting me.
-[frustrated] Mom…
-Lily, listen…
I know the danger I'm in.
And you're not the only one who's worried
that the Ardientes
will tear us apart again.
I know you're putting yourself
in grave danger
just so can we obtain justice.
But, Lily, don't give them
any reasons to suspect you.
[tense music playing]
-[heavy footsteps]
-[grunts]
[sighs]
[heavy breathing]
-What happened, Emilia?
-Auntie, where's Raul?
In his room.
Can you please tell me what happened?
I confronted that Camia woman, Auntie.
-[confused] What?!
-Yes, Auntie. I confronted her.
And I told her to keep her paws
off my husband.
But, someone got in my way.
Guess who? Ivy.
She just came out of nowhere
and pulled me.
And why would she do that?
Exactly. I don't know, either.
But, I have a feeling
she did it to protect Camia.
You know what? I smell a traitor
in our own backyard.
Are you telling me that Ivy
and Camia are working together?
Nothing's impossible, Auntie.
That's why I need to find out
how they're connected.
[Carlotta] How's your mother, Ivy?
She's fine now, Nanny Carlotta.
But, this should never happen again.
And what about you?
I'll be fine.
I just have to be careful now.
I get reckless
whenever my mother's involved.
All right. I'll get you
something to eat, okay?
Ivy. I'm sorry, I failed
to watch over Emilia.
Jepoy, it's not your fault.
Ivy, you don't understand.
It is my fault.
You don't know how much
I worried about you.
[soft music playing]
For sure, Emilia's suspecting you now.
I need to do something.
Just make sure you won't
get yourself in danger, Jepoy.
You've done so much for me.
Even things you shouldn't have done.
That's not enough, Ivy.
How's it not enough, Jepoy?
You're risking your life
every day just for me.
Just to help me with my plans.
Ivy, you don't understand.
That's not enough because I love you.
[soft music playing]
I mean, as a friend.
Ever since we were kids,
you're all I have.
You're my family and my only friend.
Remember when you saved me?
You gave my life direction.
So, there's nothing
I wouldn't do for you, Ivy.
[soft music playing]
Thank you, Jepoy.
For everything.
Take care of yourself.
[soft music playing]
Papa, you're right about Ivy.
She's just playing with us.
I don't know if she just convinced Diego,
or they've always been accomplices,
but my point is, they can't be trusted.
Emilia, we can't trust anyone anymore.
Not even your closest friends
or most loyal servants.
[sinister music playing]
Sometimes, not even your own family.
I guess that's really how it is now.
[tense music playing]
You might be allies today…
but enemies tomorrow.
[Julio chuckles]
Good thing I can easily spot
those dirty moles.
[Julio] I can smell traitors
from a mile away.
And I'll always catch them in the act.
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
[door closes]
[tense music swelling]
Grandpa, Mama…
Excuse me. You have to see this.
Spot the hero here.
[suspenseful music]
-[scoffs]
-[Emilia] Oh.
I knew it.
[Emilia] Madrigal?
Good work, Arnaldo.
We finally caught the rat.
[chuckling]
[dramatic music]
[soft music playing]
[Ivy] Where are the other witnesses?
Lily, they're all dead.
[screams]
After everything we've done!
Miss Ivy, I have a favor to ask.
Get my family out of here
so they won't get dragged into all this.
[Georgina] Mr. Vidal, did the former
governor order you to rape
and kill Camia Cruz?
No, Your Honor.
The Ardientes would've killed my family
if I didn't retract my statement.
Due to insufficient testimonies,
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo and Raul Torillo…
are hereby declared innocent
of the rape, abduction,
and illegal imprisonment of Camia Cruz.
Mom.
Lily.
More innocents have died
at the hands of the Ardientes.
I can't stop thinking that
if it weren't for us,
this wouldn't have happened.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Mom…
Don't say that.
We didn't do anything wrong.
What the Ardientes did is not our fault.
If we let them overwhelm us,
no one else will have
the courage to fight them.
Let them gloat.
If they think they've won,
they're wrong.
Because I'll never give up.
We'll never give up.
[action music playing]
[Julio] What do you mean?
Tonio was able to leave
the country without us knowing?
[Arnaldo] Someone helped them.
[Emilia] The question is, who?
Camia doesn't have the resources
to do that.
[Arnaldo] I'm suspecting Senator Magno,
but we're not sure yet.
[Emilia] How can we make sure
Tonio will keep quiet?
[Arnaldo] After I threatened
Tonio and his family,
I'm sure he'll keep his mouth shut.
One more slip-up, and I'll wipe them out.
Just like I took care of
all the other witnesses.
[Emilia] As for me,
I'll silence Camia once and for all
to solve our problem.
[Julio] Slow down, Emilia.
She's too high a risk
to take on right now.
[Magno] Oh, thank you.
[tense music playing]
Senator Magno? Senator,
it's so nice to see you here!
-Hi, Miss Aguas!
-Hello!
Have you met my wife?
Cecil, this is Ivy Aguas.
-Hello!
-Hi, Cecil. Nice to meet you.
Senator, I'm so sorry
I disturbed your date night.
It's okay.
I hope we can arrange a meeting soon?
A meeting? For what?
Aren't you supporting the
Ardientes with their campaign?
[chuckles]
Senator, with the controversies
piling up against the Ardientes,
I don't know if it's the right decision
to keep supporting them.
I want to support someone
who has principles…
a firm resolve, and a heart
for the common people.
I hope I'm talking
to the right person now.
Okay, I'll tell my secretary to call you.
Thank you, Senator. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Enjoy. Enjoy your date.
Nice meeting you, Cecil!
Senator, thank you.
You're welcome.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
[line ringing]
[door opening]
Hands up!
[line ringing]
-You recorded it.
-[line ringing]
Who's on the phone? Give me that.
[Arnaldo grunts]
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
Hey!
[Jepoy and Arnaldo grunting]
[phone ringing]
Jepoy?
[action music playing]
[Arnaldo] Give me that! Give it to me!
[goon] Take it.
Hold him still. Make him stand.
[action music playing]
Good. Very well-played, Madrigal.
I don't need to scare you, do I?
You know what I do to our enemies.
So, spit it out.
Come on. Spit it out! Out with it!
[Jepoy grunts]
-[goon] Stand up!
-Come on. Spit it out.
Spit it out!
[action music playing]
[Jepoy coughing]
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
[action music playing]
[brooding music playing]
He's all yours.
I want you to search his room thoroughly.
I want to know exactly
who this bastard works for.
[brooding music playing]
You're wasting your time.
You'll never get anything from me.
[goon] Sir.
Nothing, huh?
Hmm…
Hey.
How are you connected to Magno?
Is he your boss?
[breathing heavily]
Well?!
[Julio chuckles]
He's tough, Grandpa. We
won't get him to spill anything.
Arnaldo, I've seen a lot
of tough men in my life.
So let's test how tough he really is.
Take him to the dungeon.
Go!
[line ringing]
Ivy, are you okay?
No, I'm not.
Because Jepoy's
still not answering his phone.
He rang my phone last night.
But he didn't pick up
when I tried to call him back.
I'm worried about him, Diego.
Jepoy always gives me updates
on what the Ardientes are up to.
I'll ask my dad.
No! No.
Don't you dare do that.
Didn't I tell you
that I don't trust your father?
What if he puts Jepoy's life in danger?
[tense music playing]
Maybe I should just go
to the Ardientes' mansion?
Don't. Ivy, the Ardientes are
growing suspicious of you now.
What if they're just setting you up?
I don't care. I need to save Jepoy.
Is that how important Jepoy is to you?
Yes.
Yes, Diego.
Jepoy's important to me.
He's done so much for me.
He's sacrificed a lot just
so I can carry out my plans.
That's why I need to do
something to save Jepoy.
[melancholic music playing]
Don't worry. I'll call you, okay?
Um… I'll just get changed.
-Ouch!
-Be careful. Your wound is deep.
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
I'm okay now.
No, you should rest first.
No, Diego. I'm fine. Thank you.
Ivy, you need to rest.
I need to get moving.
We both know the Ardientes
are already making
their move as we speak.
We have no idea who they're torturing
or who they'll kill next.
That's why I need to act now.
-Ivy.
-Emilia.
What brings you here?
Uh…
Are you still upset with me?
I was worried you got offended
by what I did.
So, I brought you some flowers
as a peace offering.
Thank you. But, it's okay,
don't worry about it.
Wait, can I offer you anything?
Juice, coffee, tea, or wine?
-Water would be fine.
-All right.
I'll just bring this to the kitchen
and put it in a vase to keep them fresh.
-Okay.
-Hold on.
-I'll just stay here.
-Maid, come with me.
Throw this away.
[sinister music playing]
You know what, Madrigal?
I'm mad because I was outwitted.
But do you know what makes me feel worse?
It's the fact that I was
outwitted by a mere bodyguard!
[grunts]
You bastard! I trusted you!
And this is how you repay me?!
Hmm?!
Hey! Don't doze off! Open your eyes!
I'm not done with you!
I'm just getting started!
I'll make you pay, Madrigal.
I'll teach you a lesson,
one you won't forget.
Does it hurt?!
[Jepoy retches]
Go on! Spit it out! Go ahead!
Bastard!
[coughing]
Congressman, Mrs. Emilia's on the phone.
Hello?
Hello, Papa.
Ivy's here. Can I bring her there?
Why? What are you up to?
This is Papa's happy place. Surprise.
[Julio] I just want you to see
what we do to anyone
who betrays the Ardientes!
I need to save Jepoy.
I will never forgive myself
if something bad happens to you.
And I won't forgive myself
if I let them kill Jepoy!
You will tell me who your boss is.
If you don't, I'll drill this
into your forehead.
Okay, Grandpa. I'll take care of
Camia Cruz. You can count on me.
Go on. Break into the house.
[theme music playing]